jambajuice.com 2010-11-20

# Privacy Policy | Jamba Juice

**Our Commitment to Privacy**

It is the policy of Jamba Juice Company to respect your privacy. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices at www.jambajuice.com (the 'Site') and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. This notice applies only to information collected or submitted on the Site. By using the Site, you agree to the collection and use of your information as described herein. We reserve the right to change these terms and will post any changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect and how we use it. We encourage you to check this page regularly. Your continued use of the Site following any changes will constitute your acceptance of such changes.

**The Information We Collect**

There are several types of information we collect on the Site. On some pages on the Site, you can voluntarily provide personally identifiable information such as your name, postal address, e-mail address and phone number when you contact us with an inquiry, request, or suggestion, provide feedback on our products, participate in a marketing program, or register to receive promotional materials. If you are interested in applying for a job at Jamba Juice Company, we may collect your resume. Holders of a jambacard may voluntarily register their cards on the Site or by telephone. When you purchase, register or reload your jambacard, we collect the personally identifiable information listed above, financial information (credit card numbers, credit card expiration dates, billing address, etc.), and user profile and preferences information. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from visitors to the Site who are under thirteen years of age.

**The Way We Use Information ** ****

****

Except as disclosed in this notice, we do not sell or disclose your personally identifiable information to third parties without providing you an opportunity to opt out or otherwise prohibit such use. We may access, use or disclose your personally identifiable information to operate, maintain, service or improve the Site; provide targeted e-mails, surveys, or promotional offers to you; analyze the Site to make it more effective; or for other general internal business purposes.

In connection with the jambacard, we will use the information collected to create an easy-to-use and convenient way to process your transactions and provide you information about your jambacard balance. Financial information is not used for any other purpose than billing.

We may use third party contractors to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as authorize credit card transactions. We may share your personally identifiable information with these contractors for those limited purposes.

If Jamba Juice Company is sold to or merges with another company, some or all of the information collected from you may be transferred to a third party as a result of the transfer of assets. We may also disclose your information when we determine it is necessary to comply with applicable laws or protect the interests or safety or Jamba Juice or other visitors to the Site.

**Opt-Out / Opt-Out**

If you would like to make sure we do not share your email address or other customer information with any third parties or that we not provide you with targeted e-mails, surveys or promotional offers, send us an e-mail opting out of these communications to [unsubscribe@jambajuice.com](mailto:unsubscribe@jambajuice.com). Please note that we may occasionally contact you for administrative purposes even if you opt out of these communications.

If Jamba Juice Company is sold to or merges with another company, some or all of the information collected from you may be transferred to a third party as a result of the transfer of assets. We may also disclose your information when we determine it is necessary to comply with applicable laws or protect the interests or safety or Jamba Juice or other visitors to the Site.

**Links**

The Site may contain links to other sites, including among others those of advertisers and other third parties and companies whose trademarks appear on the Site. We are not responsible for the information collection practices or the content of the sites to which we link.

**How You Can Access or Correct Your Information**

You can access, change, or delete information pertaining to your jambacard registration at the Manage Profile section after you have signed into your account on the Site. You can also change other personally identifiable information you have provided to us, by going to the [Contact Us](http://www.jambajuice.com/contactus) section of the Site, and sending us an e-mail request.

**Security**

In connection with the jambacard, your personally identifiable and financial information are encrypted using SSL (Secure Socket Layer) encryption technology before being sent over the Internet. This is industry standard technology designed to protect the security of your information. To help prevent unauthorized access to your data, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have also established physical, electronic, and managerial procedures designed to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this privacy policy or our use of your information, please call us at 1-866-4R-FRUIT, [Contact Us](http://www.jambajuice.com/contactus) via e-mail or write to us at Jamba Juice Support Center, 6475 Christie Avenue, Suite 150, Emeryville, CA 94608.

For privacy or security questions regarding the jambacard, please call us at 1-866-4R-FRUIT or contact us via e-mail at [jambacard@jambajuice.com](mailto:jambacard@jambajuice.com) or write to us at Jamba Juice Support Center, 6475 Christie Avenue, Suite 150, Emeryville, CA 94608.

****
